A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Publications (Non-Grant Related), Accession 2017:050 FA1304
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Ford Foundation Publications, 1
  - Women's Studies: A Retrospective, A Report to the Ford Foundation, Beverly Guy-Sheftall, Susan Heath (2 copies), 1995 June (Box 14, Folder 113)
  - The Ford Foundation and the United Nations (2 copies), 1996 February (Box 14, Folder 114)
  - Relinking Life and Work: Toward a Better Future, Rhona Rapoport and Lotte Bailyn (2 copies), 1996 November (Box 14, Folder 115)
    A Report to the Ford Foundation based on a collaborative research project with three corporations
  - Population and Development: Is a Consensus Possible?, Michael S. Teitelbaum, A Ford Foundation Reprint from Foreign Affairs (2 copies), 1974 July (Box 14, Folder 116)
  - New Approaches to Conflict Resolution, A Ford Foundation Report (2 copies), 1978 May (Box 14, Folder 117)
  - Poor Rural Women: A Policy Perspective, Adrienne Germain (2 copies), 1966-1967 (Box 14, Folder 118)
    A Ford Foundation Reprint from the Journal of International Affairs
  - The Theater as Liturgy, Ford Foundation Reprint, Roger G. Kennedy (2 copies), 1978 November 12 (Box 14, Folder 119)
  - C3I in Foundation Work, McGeorge Bundy, A Ford Foundation Report (2 copies), 1979 May (Box 14, Folder 120)
  - Confronting Man's Inhumanity, A Ford Foundation Report, Richard Magat (2 copies), 1978 December (Box 14, Folder 121)
  - What's New in Dispute Resolution, Mitchell Sviridoff (2 copies), 1980 May 21 (Box 14, Folder 122)
    A Ford Foundation Reprint from New York Law Journal
  - Ford Foundation - Applying for Grants (2 copies), 1980 (Box 14, Folder 123)
  - Current Interests of the Ford Foundation (2 copies), 1980 June (Box 14, Folder 124)
  - LISC - Chicago (2 copies), undated (Box 14, Folder 125)
    LISC - Local Initiatives Support Corporation
  - LISC, The Local Initiatives Support Corporations, A Private-Public Venture for Community and Neighborhood Revitalization, The LISC South Bronx Program (2 copies), undated (Box 14, Folder 126)
  - Crossing Borders: Revitalizing Area Studies (2 copies), 1999 April (Box 14, Folder 127)
  - Poblacion y Desarollo: ¿Es Posible Llegar a un Consenso?, Michael S. Teitelbaum (2 copies), 1974 July (Box 14, Folder 128)
    Reproducida de Foreign Affairs por la Fundacion Ford
  - Population et Developpement: Peut-On S'Entendre?, Michael S. Teitelbaum (2 copies), 1974 July (Box 14, Folder 129)
    Une reproduction de la Fondation Ford de Foreign Affairs
  - The Rationale for International Assistance to Population Programs in the Developing World, Oscar Harkavy (2 copies), 1973 (Box 14, Folder 130)
    A Ford Foundation Reprint from International Journal of Health Services
  - About the Ford Foundation (2 different pamphlets), 1972 January, 1963 May; 1963 May (Box 14, Folder 131)
  - An Old Tradition in a New Day: Private Institutions in the Public Service, McGeorge Bundy, A Ford Foundation Reprint (2 copies), 1973 November 2 (Box 14, Folder 132)
  - Las Naciones Unidas en su Segundo Cincuentenario (2 copies), undated (Box 15, Folder 133)
    Informe del Grupo de Trabajo Independiente sobre el futuro de las Naciones Unidas
  - Philanthropy and Public Schools: One Foundation's Evolving Perspective, Edward Meade, Jr. (2 copies), 1979 June 8 (Box 15, Folder 134)
    A Ford Foundation Reprint from Private Philanthropy and Public Elementary and Secondary Education, A Rockefeller Archive Center Publication
  - The Preservation of the Cosmopolitan Research University in the United States, Elinor G. Barber and Warren Ilchman, (2 copies), 1980 May (Box 15, Folder 135)
    A Ford Foundation Reprint from the Annals
  - Delivering on a Promise to Advance Human Welfare (2 copies), 2006 (Box 15, Folder 136)
  - Frontiers in Reproduction and Fertility Control Part 2: A Review of the Reproductive Sciences and Contraceptive Development, Roy O. Greep and Marjorie A. Koblinsky (2 copies), 1977 (Box 15, Folder 137)
    Sponsored by the Ford Foundation
  - Language and Development: A Retrospective Survey of Ford Foundation Language Projects 1952-1974 (2 copies), 1975 (Box 15, Folder 138)
  - City High Schools: A Recognition of Progress, A Ford Foundation Report, Sue Koch (2 copies), 1984 (Box 16, Folder 139)
    Paperbacks, for hardcover refer to box 18
  - American Workers Abroad, A Report to the Ford Foundation, Robert Schrank (2 copies), 1979 (Box 16, Folder 140)
  - The Miami Riot of 1980 Crossing the Bounds, Bruce Porter and Marvin Dunn, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 141)
  - One Nation, So Many Governments, A Report to the Ford Foundation, Michael N. Danielson, Alan M. Hershey, and John M. Bayne (2 copies) (Box 16, Folder 142)
  - Language and Development: A Retrospective Survey of Ford Foundation Language Projects 1952-1974, Case Studies (2 copies), 1975 (Box 17, Folder 143, Box 112, Folder 1304)
  - Assistance to Third World Broadcasters, Miriam Williford, Ford Foundation/British Broadcasting Companies (2 copies), 1979 (Box 17, Folder 144)
  - Women in the Military: Changes at Home, Lessons for Abroad in Peace and War, Appendix 7, Women's Research and Education Institute, 1994 December (Box 17, Folder 145)
  - Testing Assumptions: A Survey of Teacher's Attitudes Toward the Nation's School Reform Agenda, LH Research, Louis Harris, Robert F. Wagner, Jr., 1993 September (Box 17, Folder 146)
  - Redeeming the American Promise, Report of the Panel on Educational Opportunity and Postsecondary Desegregation, Southern Education Foundation (2 copies), 1995 (Box 18, Folder 147)
  - City High Schools: A Recognition of Progress, A Ford Foundation Report, Sue Koch, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 148)
    Hardcover, for paperbacks refer to box 16
  - Dancing: A Ford Foundation Report, Elizabeth Kendall (2 copies), 1983 December (Box 18, Folder 149, Box 112, Folder 1308)
  - Sharps and Flats: A Report on Ford Foundation Assistance to American Music, 1980 July (Box 18, Folder 150)
  - Fires in the Mirror: Crown Heights, Brooklyn and Other Identities, Essays and Teaching Strategies, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 151)
  - A Fundação Ford no Brasil, The Ford Foundation in Brazil, 2002-2003 (Box 18, Folder 152)
  - A Fundação Ford no Brasil, The Ford Foundation in Brazil, 1998-1999 (Box 18, Folder 153)
  - Os Anos da Fundação Ford no Brasil, The Ford Foundation's 40 Years in Brazil a Partnership for Social Change (2 copies), 2002 (Box 18, Folder 154, Box 112, Folder 1303)
  - Fundação Ford Brasil, Ford Foundation Brazil, undated (Box 18, Folder 155)
  - Celebrating Indonesia: Fifty Years with the Ford Foundation 1953-2003 (Box 19, Folder 156)
  - GrantCraft Publications, Practical Wisdom for Grantmakers (34 publications), 2002-2010 (Box 19, Folder 157-159)
    Folder 157): Roles@work playing cards; Saying Yes, Saying No to Applicants; Using Competitors and Requests for Proposals (RFPs); Building Community Inside and Out with a Good Neighbor Committee; When Projects Flounder: Coming to the Rescue When Good Grants Go Astray; Scanning the Landscape: Finding Out What's Going on in Your Field; Providing for the Long Term: Supporting Endowments and Investable Assets; Folder 158): Working with Start-ups, Grant Makers and New Organizations; Grant Making with a Gender Lens; Funder Collaboratives: Why and How Funders Work Together; Communicating for Impact: Strategies for Grantmakers (2 copies); Grants to Individuals: Investing in People and their Communities; Funding Community Organizations: Social Change Through Civic Participation; Program-Related Investing: Skills and Strategies for New PRI Funders; The Effective Exit: Managing the End of a Funding Relationship; Grant Making with a Racial Equity Lens; Folder 159): Executive Transitions: Grant Makers and Nonprofit Leadership Change; Advocacy Funding: The Philanthropy of Changing Minds; Working with the Business Sector: Pursuing Public Good with Private Partners; International Grant Making: Funding with a Global View; World Summits and Conferences: Grant Making on a Global Stage; Working With Government: Guidance for Grantmakers; Personal Strategy: Mobilizing Your Self for Effective Grant Making; Making Measures Work for You: Outcomes and Evaluation; Working with Intermediaries: Global Grant Making Through Partner Organizations; Scanning and Networking: Routines for Discovering the Unexpected; Accessing and Managing PRI Risk: Nothing Ventured, Nothing Gained; Getting Inside the Story: Ethnographic Approaches to Evaluation; Learning Together: Collaborative Inquiry Among Grant Makers and Grantees; Mapping Change: Using a Theory of Change to Guide Planning and Evaluation; Participatory Action Research: Involving "All the Players" in Evaluation and Change; Case Study: Building Financial Strength and Program Quality: A Case on Grant Making to Strengthen Community Foundations; Case Study: Inheriting a Grant Portfolio: A Case on Grant Making in Water Management; Case Study: Programming on a Blank Slate: A Case on Grant Making in Rural Poverty; Catalog
  - The Partnership for Higher Education in Africa - African Universities: Stories of Change, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 160)
  - The Ford Foundation in China, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 161)
  - The Ford Foundation and the International Center for Tropical Agriculture (CIAT): From Inception to Impact: Partners for Food Security and Prosperity, 2010 (Box 20, Folder 162)
  - Ford Foundation Office for the Andean Region and Southern Cone, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 163)
  - Ford Foundation at a Glance (2 copies) and Trustee Handbook, 2000, 2004; 2004 (Box 20, Folder 164)
  - Ford Foundation Building and Garden Brochures, 1967, 1992; 1992 (Box 20, Folder 165)
    Ford Foundation building and garden in New York City and the Ford Foundation Building and Gardens, Lodi Estate, New Delhi
  - Activities in the Creative and Performing Arts Architecture/Urban Revitalization, 1957-1980, 1980 September 30 (Box 20, Folder 166)
  - Activities in the Creative and Performing Arts Support for Women's Programs, 1957-1980, The Ford Foundation Office of the Arts, 1980 September 30 (Box 20, Folder 167)
  - Activities in the Creative and Performing Arts: Music, 1957-1980, 1980 September 30 (Box 20, Folder 168)
  - Activities in the Creative and Performing Arts Creative Writing/Literacy, 1957-1980, 1980 September 30 (Box 20, Folder 169)
  - Activities in the Creative and Performing Arts Film, 1957-1980, 1980 September 30 (Box 20, Folder 170)
  - Activities in the Creative and Performing Arts Dance, 1957-1980, 1980 September 30 (Box 20, Folder 171)
  - Activities in the Creative and Performing Arts Theater, 1957-1980, 1980 September 30 (Box 20, Folder 172)
  - Activities in the Creative and Performing Arts Social Development Grants, 1957-1980, 1980 September 30 (Box 20, Folder 173)
  - Activities in the Creative and Performing Arts Visual Arts, 1957-1980, 1980 September 30 (Box 20, Folder 174)
  - Learning by Television, The Fund for Advancement of Education, Judith Murphy and Ronald Gross, 1966 August (Box 20, Folder 175)
  - Copyright and Intellectual Property, Fund for the Advancement of Education, Julius J. Marke (2 copies), 1967 January (Box 20, Folder 176)
  - Ford Foundation Publications and Films, 1982 November, 1985 May; 1985-05 (Box 20, Folder 177)
  - Ford Foundation Grants in Resources and Environment, 1968 June (Box 20, Folder 178)
  - The Ford Foundation and Pakistan, A Ford Foundation Pictorial Report (2 copies), 1959 May (Box 20, Folder 179, Box 111, Folder 1300)
  - Educational Television, ETV, A Ford Foundation Pictorial Report (2 copies), 1961 March (Box 21, Folder 180)
  - Breaking the Credentials Barrier, S. M. Miller, A Ford Foundation Reprint (2 copies), 1967 March 23 (Box 21, Folder 181)
  - The Changing School Curriculum, A Report from the Fund for the Advancement of Education, John I. Goodlad (2 copies), 1966 August (Box 21, Folder 182)
  - The Apprentice Experts (3 copies), 1964 February (Box 21, Folder 183)
  - Four Case Studies of Programmed Instruction, Fund for the Advancement of Education, 1964 June (Box 21, Folder 184)
  - Decade of Experiment: The Fund for the Advancement of Education 1951-1961 (Box 21, Folder 185)
  - The Public Stake in Private Service, Henry T. Heald, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 186)
  - Faculty Power, Reprinted from The Atlantic Monthly, McGeorge Bundy, 1968 September (Box 21, Folder 187)
  - Education in the Developing Countries, F. F. Hill (2 copies), 1962 (Box 21, Folder 188)
    A Ford Foundation Reprint from International Development Review, Vol. IV, No. 4, December 1962; The article is a condensed version of a lecture delivered at the Cornell University Summer School Lecture Series, July 11, 1962
  - India's "Food Miracle," Ernest Dunbar (2 copies), 1968 March 19 (Box 21, Folder 189)
    A Ford Foundation Reprint from LOOK, March 19, 1968, Volume 32, No. 6
  - In Common Cause: Relations Between Higher Education and Foundations, Henry T. Heald (2 copies), 1963 November 13 (Box 21, Folder 190)
    Address to the 7th annual meeting of the Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges in Chicago
  - Scholars' Work and Works (2 copies), undated (Box 21, Folder 191)
    Pertains to university press and research library projects in the 1960s(?)
  - The Arts and Philanthropy, W. McNeil Lowry (2 copies), 1962 December 10 (Box 21, Folder 192)
    Delivered at Brandeis University, Poses Institute of Fine Arts
  - The Ford Foundation and National Affairs, A Ford Foundation Reprint, Mitchell Sviridoff (2 copies), 1971 April 28 (Box 21, Folder 193)
    Remarks by Mitchell Sviridoff delivered at the Foundation Luncheon Group in New York City
  - Architects of Order (2 copies), 1961 September (Box 21, Folder 194)
    Pertains to the study of law
  - About the Ford Foundation (2 solid blue copies, 2 half dark blue copies, and 1 half teal copy), 1965 March, 1967 January, 1968 September; 1967-01; 1965-03 (Box 21, Folder 195)
  - The Pay of Professors, A Report on the Ford Foundation Grants for College-Teacher Salaries (2 copies), 1962 February (Box 22, Folder 196)
  - The Ford Foundation Development Program in Africa, Francis X. Sutton (2 copies), 1960 December (Box 22, Folder 197)
    A Ford Foundation Reprint from the African Studies Bulletin, Vol. III, No. IV, December 1960
  - International Legal Studies, John B. Howard (2 copies), 1959 (Box 22, Folder 198)
    A Ford Foundation Reprint from the University of Chicago Law Review, Vol. 26, Summer, 1959
  - The Ford Foundation and the States of Alabama, Florida, Georgia, Louisiana, and Mississippi: A Report of Grants to Organizations and Individuals from 1936 to September 30, 1958 (2 copies), 1959 January (Box 22, Folder 199)
  - Ford Foundation Grants in Alabama, Louisiana, and Mississippi (2 copies), 1964 April (Box 22, Folder 200)
    A report on grants to organizations, institutions, and individuals in the states of Alabama, Louisiana, and Mississippi from 1950 to February 1964
  - Ford Foundation Grants in Alaska and Hawaii, 1965 March (Box 22, Folder 201)
    A report on grants to organizations, institutions, and individuals in the States of Alaska and Hawaii from 1950 to January 31, 1965
  - The Ford Foundation and the States of Arizona, Colorado, New Mexico, and Texas, A Report of Grants to Organizations and Individuals from 1936 to March 31, 1959, 1959 August (Box 22, Folder 202)
  - Ford Foundation Grants in Arizona, Nevada, and New Mexico (2 copies), 1964 September (Box 22, Folder 203)
    A report on grants to organizations, institutions, and individuals in the States of Arizona, Nevada, and New Mexico from 1950 to July 31, 1964
  - Ford Foundation Grants in Arkansas, 1965 June (Box 22, Folder 204)
    A report on grants to organizations, institutions, and individuals in the State of Arkansas from 1950 to April 15, 1965
  - The Ford Foundation and the State of California, A Report of Grants to Organizations and Individuals in California from 1936 to September 30, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 205)
  - Ford Foundation Grants in Colorado (2 copies), 1964 July (Box 22, Folder 206)
    A report on grants to organizations, institutions, and individuals in the state of California from 1950 to May 31, 1964
  - Ford Foundation Grants in Connecticut (2 copies), 1964 June (Box 22, Folder 207)
    A report on grants to organizations, institutions, and individuals in the State of Connecticut from 1944 to April 30, 1964
  - Ford Foundation Grants in Delaware and Maryland (2 copies), 1965 April (Box 22, Folder 208)
    A report on grants to organizations, institutions, individuals, in the states of Delaware and Maryland from 1950 to January 31, 1965
  - Ford Foundation Grants in the District of Columbia, 1965 March (Box 22, Folder 209)
    A report on grants to organizations, institutions, and individuals in the District of Columbia from 1938 to December 1, 1964
  - Ford Foundation Grants in Florida (2 copies), 1964 April (Box 22, Folder 210)
    A report on grants to organizations, institutions, and individuals in the state of Florida from 1950 to February 1964
  - Ford Foundation Grants in Georgia (2 copies), 1963 May (Box 22, Folder 211)
    A report on grants to organizations, institutions, and individuals in the state of Georgia from 1949 to March 15, 1963
  - Ford Foundation Grants in Idaho, North Dakota, and South Dakota, 1965 June (Box 22, Folder 212)
    A report on grants to organizations, institutions, and individuals in the states of Idaho, North Dakota, and South Dakota from 1950 to April 30, 1965
  - Ford Foundation Grants in Illinois, 1964 February (Box 22, Folder 213)
    A report on grants to organizations, institutions, and individuals in the state of Illinois from 1950 to October 31, 1963
  - Ford Foundation Grants in Indiana (2 copies), 1963 (Box 22, Folder 214)
    A report on Ford Foundation grants to organizations, institutions, and individuals in the state of Indiana from 1950 to March 1, 1963
  - Tapestry for Tomorrow: The Ford Foundation Program in the Middle East (2 copies), 1964 February (Box 22, Folder 215)
  - The Society of the Streets (2 copies), 1965 November (Box 22, Folder 216)
  - American Foundations in Non-Western Areas, Francis X. Sutton (2 copies), 1961 March (Box 22, Folder 217)
  - Problems of Tropical Agriculture, Herbert R. Albrecht (2 copies), 1970 May (Box 22, Folder 218)
    A Ford Foundation Reprint from Standard Bank Review
  - A More Effective Arm: A Report on a Police Development Fund, Newly Established by the Ford Foundation (2 copies), 1970 August (Box 22, Folder 219)
    The name of the Police Development Fund changed to the Police Foundation after the publication of this report.
  - English as a Second Language: Development and Testing, Melvin J. Fox and David Harris (2 copies), 1964 (Box 22, Folder 220)
    A Ford Foundation Reprint from Overseas, Vol. 3, No. 5, January 1964
  - Financial Support of Women's Programs in the 1970s: A Review of Private and Governmental Funding in the United States and Abroad, A Report to the Ford Foundation (2 copies), 1979 July (Box 22, Folder 221, Box 112, Folder 1302)
  - Accountability and Governance in Public Education, Edward J. Meade, Jr. (2 copies), 1968 (Box 23, Folder 222)
    Adapted from an address given before the Committee on the Smaller Secondary School at the annual convention of the National Association Secondary School Principals, Atlantic City, New Jersey, February 12, 1968
  - Community Action: A Response to Some Unfinished Business, Paul N. Ylvisaker (2 copies), 1963 (Box 23, Folder 223)
    Major excerpts from an address before the Citizens' Conference on Community Planning in Indianapolis, Indiana, January 11, 1963
  - America the Resilient, F. Champion Ward (2 copies), 1969 (Box 23, Folder 224)
    A Ford Foundation Reprint from the Journal of Higher Education, Volume XL, Number 6, p 421-429
  - Research in Reproductive Biology and Contraceptive Technology: Present Status and Needs for the Future, Oscar Harkavy and John Maier (2 copies), 1970 (Box 23, Folder 225)
    A Ford Foundation Reprint from Family Planning Perspectives, Vol. 2, No, 3, June 1970
  - Golden Years?, Walter E. Ashley (2 copies), 1963 November (Box 23, Folder 226)
  - The Ford Foundation Program in Pakistan, George F. Gant (2 copies), 1959 (Box 23, Folder 227)
    A Ford Foundation Reprint from the Annals of the American Academy of Political and Social Science, Vol. 323, May 1959
  - Report of the Trustees of the Ford Foundation (2 copies), 1950 September 27 (Box 23, Folder 228, Box 110, Folder 1292)
  - The Difference It Makes (2 copies), 1957 (Box 23, Folder 229)
    Describes grants given to voluntary hospitals to extend and improve services in December 1955
  - The Wealth of a Nation (2 copies), 1959 June (Box 23, Folder 230)
    Economic projects
  - The Good Seed: A Report on the Ford Foundation's Continuing Investment in Education (2 copies), 1957 (Box 23, Folder 231)
  - The Nonprofit Motive, H. Rowan Gaither, Jr. (2 copies), 1960 January (Box 23, Folder 232)
    An address before the Bond Club of New York, October 24, 1956, by H. Rowan Gaither, Jr.
  - The Ford Foundation Program in Humanities and the Arts (2 copies), 1959 February (Box 23, Folder 233)
  - The Ford Foundation and St. Louis (2 copies), 1957 (Box 23, Folder 234)
  - The Ford Foundation and Foreign Affairs, H. Rowan Gaither, Jr., President of the Ford Foundation, 1956 May 3 (Box 23, Folder 235)
    An address delivered at the 25-year service dinner of Dunwoody Industrial Institute, Minneapolis, Minnesota
  - The Ford Foundation Program in Pakistan (2 copies), 1964 (Box 23, Folder 236)
    Summarizes Ford Foundation grants in Pakistan from 1955 to September 1964
  - American Community Development: Preliminary Reports by Directors of Projects Assisted by the Ford Foundation in Four Cities and a State (2 copies), 1964 October 1 (Box 23, Folder 237)
    Twenty-Ninth Annual Conference, National Association of Housing and Redevelopment Officials, Denver, Colorado
    Boston, New Haven, Oakland, Philadelphia, and North Carolina
  - The Ford Foundation Charter and Bylaws, 1966 December 8 (Box 23, Folder 238)
  - American Foundations and the Common Welfare, Henry T. Heald (2 copies), 1965 (Box 23, Folder 239)
    Address given at Columbia University on March 5, 1965 to a group of foreign scholars teaching or conducting research in universities and other institutions in the New York metropolitan area
  - Ford Foundation in East and Central Africa (2 copies), 1969 June (Box 23, Folder 240)
    Summarizes Ford Foundation grants and work in the region from 1958-1969
  - The Ford Foundation Program in North Africa (2 copies), 1964 (Box 23, Folder 241)
    Describes work and grants in the region from 1961-1964
  - The Ford Foundation Program in Nigeria (2 copies), 1965 (Box 23, Folder 242)
    Describes grants and Ford Foundation work in Nigeria from 1959 to 1965
  - Publications from the Ford Foundation (2 copies), 1973 June (Box 23, Folder 243)
  - Current Trends in Population Control, Nicholson J. Eastman (2 copies), 1964 (Box 23, Folder 244)
    A Ford Foundation Reprint from Fertility and Sterility, Vol. 15, No. 5, September-October 1964
  - Schools and the Environment, Edward A. Ames (2 copies), 1969 (Box 23, Folder 245)
    A Ford Foundation Reprint - prepared for the American Nature Study Society, December 27, 1969
  - Essentials of Manpower Planning in Economic Development, John F. Hilliard (2 copies), 1962 (Box 24, Folder 246)
    A Ford Foundation Reprint from International Development Review, Vol IV, No 1, March 1962
  - Education in the New Europe, Frank Bowles (2 copies), 1964 (Box 24, Folder 247)
    A Ford Foundation Reprint from Daedalus, Vol. 93, No. 1, Winter 1964
  - Decade of Philanthropy: The Ford Foundation 1951-1960, Henry T. Heald, President (2 copies) (Box 24, Folder 248)
    Excerpted from the 1960 Annual Report of the Ford Foundation